Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Motion Pictures and Audiorecordings Documenting Football
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Football game videotapes, 1923-2005; Accession 2006-A-031
  - Columbia (endzone), 1995 October 21; 1 (Box 463)
  - Columbia (Yale offense), 1995 October 21; 1 (Box 464)
  - Columbia (Yale defense), 1995 October 21; 1 (Box 465)
  - Penn (endzone), 1995 October 28; 1 (Box 466)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 466U)
  - Penn (Yale offense), 1995 October 28; 1 (Box 467)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 467U)
  - Penn (Yale defense), 1995 October 28; 1 (Box 468)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 468U)
  - Cornell, 1995 November 4; 1 (Box 469)
  - Cornell (wide sideline), 1994 November 4; 1 (Box 470)
  - Cornell (endzone), 1995 November 4; 1 (Box 471)
  - Cornell (Yale offense), 1995 November 4; 1 (Box 472)
  - Cornell (Yale defense), 1995 November 4; 1 (Box 473)
  - Cornell (Yale kicking), 1995 November 4; 1 (Box 474)
  - Princeton (Yale offense), 1995 November 10; 1 (Box 475)
  - Princeton (wide sideline), 1995 November 11; 1 (Box 476)
  - Princeton (endzone), 1995 November 11; 1 (Box 477)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 477U)
  - Princeton (Yale defense), 1995 November 11; 1 (Box 478)
  - Princeton (Yale kicking), 1995 November 11; 1 (Box 479)
  - Princeton (C-tech cable TV), 1995 November 11; 1 (Box 480)
  - Harvard (wide sideline), 1995 November 18; 1 (Box 481)
  - Harvard (endzone), 1995 November 18; 1 (Box 482)
  - Harvard (Yale offense), 1995 November 18; 1 (Box 483)
  - Harvard (Yale defense), 1995 November 18; 1 (Box 484)
  - Harvard (Yale kicking), 1995 November 18; 1 (Box 485)
  - Harvard, 1995 November 18; 3 (Box 73–75)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 73U)
  - Highlights, 1995; 1 (Box 489)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 489U1)
  - Highlights (TV 8), 1995; 1 (Box 490)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 490U)
  - Brown (wide sideline continuous), 1996 September 21; 1 (Box 491)
  - Brown (endzone), 1996 September 21; 1 (Box 492)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 492U)
  - Brown (Yale kicking), 1996 September 21; 1 (Box 493)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 493U)
  - Brown (NESN), 1996 September 21; 2 (Box 494–495)
  - UConn, 1996; 1 (Box 496)
  - UConn (endzone), 1996 September 28; 1 (Box 497)
  - UConn (Yale defense), 1996 September 28; 1 (Box 498)
  - Army, 1996 October 5; 1 (Box 626)
  - Army (Yale kicking), 1996 October 5; 1 (Box 499)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 499U)
  - Bucknell (wide sideline continuous), 1996 October 12; 1 (Box 500)
  - Bucknell (endzone), 1996 October 12; 1 (Box 501)
  - Bucknell (Yale defense), 1996 October 12; 1 (Box 502)
  - Dartmouth (wide sideline continuous), 1996 October 19; 1 (Box 503)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 503U)
  - Dartmouth (endzone), 1996 October 19; 1 (Box 504)
  - Dartmouth (Yale kicking), 1996 October 19; 1 (Box 505)
  - Columbia (wide sideline continuous), 1996 October 26; 1 (Box 506)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 506U)
  - Columbia (endzone), 1996 October 26; 1 (Box 507)
  - Penn (wide sideline continuous), 1996 November 2; 1 (Box 508)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 508U)
  - Cornell (wide sideline continuous), 1996 November 9; 1 (Box 509)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 509U)
  - Princeton (wide sideline continuous), 1996 November 16; 1 (Box 510)
  - Harvard (wide sideline continuous), 1996 November 23; 1 (Box 511)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 511U)
  - Harvard, 1996 November 23; 1 (Box 512)
  - Dartmouth, 1997 October 18; 1 (Box 513)
  - Cornell, 1997 November 8; 1 (Box 514)
  - Princeton, 1997 November 15; 1 (Box 515)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 515U)
  - Harvard, 2 copies, 1997 November 22; 2 (Box 516–517)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 516U)
  - Brown, 1997; 1 (Box 518)
  - Columbia, 1997; 1 (Box 519)
  - Harvard (JV), 1997; 1 (Box 520)
  - Penn, 1997; 1 (Box 521)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 521U)
  - UConn, 1997; 1 (Box 522)
  - Valparaiso, 1997; 1 (Box 523)
  - The Game, 1997; 1 (Box 524)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 524U)
  - Football Video, 1997; 1 (Box 525)
  - Highlight Film, 1997; 1 (Box 526)
  - Holy Cross, 1998; 1 (Box 527)
  - Holy Cross (Yale defense), 1998 September 24; 1 (Box 528)
  - Penn, 1998 October 31; 1 (Box 529)
  - Penn (wide), 1998; 1 (Box 530)
  - Harvard, 1998 November 15; 2 (Box 531–532)
    - Use copy for boxes 531-532, 1 (Box 531U)
  - Harvard (wide), 1998 November 15; 1 (Box 533)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 533U)
  - Harvard (Yale kicking), 1998; 1 (Box 535)
  - Brown, 1998; 1 (Box 536)
  - Colgate, 1998; 1 (Box 537)
  - Columbia, 1998; 1 (Box 538)
  - Cornell, 1998; 1 (Box 539)
  - Dartmouth, 1998; 1 (Box 540)
  - Princeton, 1998; 1 (Box 541)
  - UConn, 1998; 1 (Box 542)
  - Highlights, 1998; 1 (Box 543)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 543U)
  - Brown, 1999 September 18; 1 (Box 544)
  - Holy Cross, 1999 October 9; 1 (Box 545)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 545U)
  - Harvard (Direct TV), 1999; 1 (Box 547)
  - Harvard, 1999; 1 (Box 548)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 548U)
  - Harvard, 1999, 2000; 1 (Box 549)
  - University of San Diego, 1999; 1 (Box 550)
  - Ivy League Champions, 1999; 1 (Box 551)
  - Dayton, 2000 September 16; 1 (Box 552)
  - Princeton, 2000 November 11; 1 (Box 553)
  - Harvard, 2000; 1 (Box 554)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 554U1)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 554U2)
  - Harvard (TV), 2000; 1 (Box 555)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 555U)
  - Yale Bulldogs, 2000; 1 (Box 556)
  - Highlight Tape, 2000; 1 (Box 557)
  - Highlights, 2000-2001; 1 (Box 558)
  - Blue White Scrimmage, 2001 October 27; 1 (Box 559)
  - Princeton, 2001 November 1; 1 (Box 560)
  - Columbia, 2001; 2 (Box 561–562)
  - Dartmouth, 2001; 1 (Box 563)
  - Harvard, 2001; 1 (Box 564)
  - Holy Cross, 2001; 1 (Box 565)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 565U1)
  - Highlight Film, 2001; 1 (Box 566)
  - Penn, 2003 October 25; 1 (Box 567)
  - Columbia, 2003 November 1; 1 (Box 568)
  - Colgate (Time Warner Cable), 2003; 1 (Box 569)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 569U)
  - Princeton (TV), 2003; 1 (Box 570)
  - Lehigh, 2004 October 16; 1 (Box 571)
  - Princeton, 2004 November 13; 1 (Box 572)
  - Princeton, 2004; 1 (Box 573)
  - Intra squad Scrimmage, undated; 1 (Box 574)
  - Columbia, undated; 1 (Box 576)
  - Harvard, undated; 2 (Box 577–578)
  - Holy Cross (NESN), undated; 1 (Box 580)
  - Holy Cross, undated; 1 (Box 580)
  - Holy Cross, undated; 1 (Box 581)
  - Princeton, undated; 4 (Box 586–589)
  - UConn, undated; 2 (Box 590–591)
  - UNH (JV -Yale offense), undated; 2 (Box 592–593)
  - UNH (endzone), undated; 1 (Box 594)
  - Army (reel 1), undated; 1 (Box 646)
  - Dartmouth (reel 3), undated; 1 (Box 648)
  - Other football-related videotapes
    - The History of Yale Football: From Camp to Cozza, 1992 December 10; 1 (Box 595)
    - History of Football by Mike Pyle, 1993; 1 (Box 596)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 596U)
    - 300th History of Yale Football, undated; 1 (Box 597)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 597U)
    - 300th History of Yale Football, tercentennial talk, undated; 1 (Box 640)
    - History (Pudge Productions), undated; 1 (Box 598)
    - History of Yale Football, undated; 6 (Box 599–604)
    - History of Yale Football, Part I, undated; 1 (Box 649)
      - Use Copy, 1 (Box 649U)
    - 1929-1937 Football History, Part III, undated; 1 (Box 650)
    - Football History, Part IV, undated; 1 (Box 651)
    - Carm Cozza Tribute, undated; 2 (Box 605–606)
      - Use copy, 2 (Box 605U–606U)
    - Carm Cozza's Retirement Dinner, undated; 1 (Box 607)
    - Carm Cozza 25th Anniversary Dinner, undated; 1 (Box 608)
    - Carm Cozza's 30 years at Yale, 1 (Box 636)
    - Carm Cozza interviews (various TV networks), 1996; 1 (Box 642)
    - Carm Cozza on "CBS Sunday Morning", undated; 1 (Box 643)
    - Celebration of a Legend: Carm Cozza Tribute, undated; 1 (Box 644)
    - Charles M. O'Hearn, 1924; 1 (Box 609)
    - Highlight of Larry Kelley, 1934-36; 1 (Box 610)
      - Use copy, 1 (Box 610U)
    - Football with Al Hessberg, 1940s; 1 (Box 611)
    - Keith Jackson, 1977; 1 (Box 612)
    - Highlight- Jack Whitaker, 1979; 1 (Box 613)
    - The Game - 100th Anniversary of Yale-Harvard, 1983 November 28; 1 (Box 614)
    - Hawaii Trip, 1987; 1 (Box 615)
    - Coach of the Year, 1989; 1 (Box 616)
    - Interview, 1992; 1 (Box 617)
    - Interviews, 1993; 1 (Box 618)
    - Ivy Football Preview, 1993; 1 (Box 619)
    - Cornell Bus Trip, 1994; 1 (Box 620)
    - Behind the Shield: Yale Connection (Chris Hetherington -Don Martin), 2003 November 16; 1 (Box 621)
    - Chris Hetherington and Don Martin -Oakland Raiders TV, 2003 November; 1 (Box 622)
    - "Handsome Dan", 2005 April 26; 1 (Box 623)
    - Black Bursted Back-up, undated; 1 (Box 624)
    - Exhibition edit, undated; 1 (Box 627)
    - Football at Yale -The Story of a Tradition, undated; 1 (Box 628)
    - Ivy League Football, undated; 1 (Box 629)
    - The Team of 1946 - 50th Reunion, undated; 1 (Box 630)
    - Yale Football Song, undated; 1 (Box 632)
    - Yale Historical (Vol. 3), undated; 1 (Box 633)
    - Unidentified, undated; 1 (Box 634)
    - Unidentified, undated; 1 (Box 635)
- Football game films, 1936-1940; Accession 2006-A-093
  Films are 16 mm, black and white, silent. Most have strong vinegar smell and measure #2 or 3 on AD strips. Many are badly warped and buckled with deteriorating film base.
  - Rutgers, 1936; 3 (Box 1–3)
  - Dartmouth, 1936; 3 (Box 4–6)
  - Brown, 1936; 2 (Box 7–8)
  - Harvard, 1936; 3 (Box 9–11)
  - Harvard Highlight, 1936; 1 (Box 99)
  - Colgate, 1936; 2 (Box 12–13)
  - Colgate Scrubs, 1936; 1 (Box 14)
  - Princeton, 1936; 1 (Box 39)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 39U)
  - Princeton Highlights, 1936; 1 (Box 15)
  - Penn, 1936; 2 (Box 74–75)
  - Maine, 1937; 2 (Box 16–17)
  - Army, 1937; 3 (Box 18–20)
  - Cornell & Army, 1937; 1 (Box 21)
  - Cornell, 1937; 3 (Box 22–24)
  - Dartmouth, 1937; 1 (Box 25)
  - Brown, 1937; 2 (Box 26–27)
  - Harvard, 1937; 2 (Box 28, Box 67)
  - Princeton/Harvard, 1937; 1 (Box 29)
  - Penn, 1937; 2 (Box 76–77)
  - Columbia, 1938; 2 (Box 30–31)
  - Navy, 1938; 2 (Box 32–33)
  - Dartmouth, 1938; 3 (Box 34–36)
  - Brown, 1938; 2 (Box 37–38)
  - Cornell vs. Penn State, 1938; 1 (Box 105)
  - Princeton, 1938; 2 (Box 40–41)
  - Harvard, 1938; 2 (Box 42–43)
  - Penn, 1938; 2 (Box 78–79)
  - Freshmen vs. Roxbury, 1938; 2 (Box 44–45)
  - Season highlights, 1938; 1 (Box 106)
  - Columbia, 1939; 2 (Box 46–47)
  - Army, 1939; 3 (Box 48–50)
  - Michigan, 1939; 2 (Box 51–52)
  - Dartmouth, 1939; 4 (Box 53–56)
  - Brown, 1939; 4 (Box 57–60)
  - Princeton, 1939; 4 (Box 61–64)
  - Harvard, 1939; 4 (Box 65–66, Box 68–69)
  - Harvard Highlights, 1939; 2 (Box 70–71)
  - Penn, 1939; 2 (Box 72–73)
  - Virginia, 1940; 3 (Box 80–82)
  - Dartmouth, 1940; 3 (Box 83–85)
    - Use copy for boxes 83-85, 1 (Box 83U)
  - Navy, 1940; 3 (Box 86–88)
  - Cornell, 1940; 3 (Box 89–91)
  - Princeton, 1940; 3 (Box 92–94)
  - Harvard, 1940; 2 (Box 95–96)
  - Brown, 1940; 3 (Box 97–98, Box 100)
  - Penn, 1940; 4 (Box 101–104)
- Football game films, 1941-1947; Accession 2006-A-127
  - Cornell, 1941; 2 (Box 1–2)
  - Virginia Highlights, 1941; 1 (Box 3)
  - Dartmouth, 1941; 1 (Box 4)
  - Harvard, 1941; 1 (Box 5)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 5U)
  - Brown, 1941; 1 (Box 6)
  - Army, 1941; 1 (Box 7)
  - Penn, 1941; 1 (Box 8)
  - Princeton, 1941; 1 (Box 9)
  - Spring Practice, 1941; 1 (Box 10)
  - Fall Scrimmage, 1941; 1 (Box 11)
  - Lehigh, 1942; 1 (Box 12)
  - Navy, 1942; 1 (Box 13)
  - Harvard, 1942; 1 (Box 14)
  - Dartmouth, 1942; 1 (Box 15)
  - Princeton, 1942; 1 (Box 16)
  - Cornell, 1942; 1 (Box 17)
  - Brown, 1942; 1 (Box 18)
  - Season Highlights, 1942; 1 (Box 19)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 19U)
  - July practice, 1942; 1 (Box 20)
  - Kings Point, 1943; 1 (Box 21)
  - Brown, 1943; 1 (Box 22)
  - Columbia, 1943; 1 (Box 23)
  - Dartmouth, 1943; 1 (Box 24)
  - Muhlenberg, 1943; 1 (Box 25)
  - Penn, 1943; 1 (Box 26)
  - Princeton, 1943; 1 (Box 27)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 27U)
  - Coast Guard, 1943; 2 (Box 28, Box 51)
  - Subbase/Holy Cross/Inter squad, 1944; 1 (Box 29)
  - Virginia, 1944; 1 (Box 30)
  - Dartmouth, 1944; 1 (Box 31)
  - Coastguard Scrimmage, 1944; 1 (Box 32)
  - Coastguard, 1944; 1 (Box 33)
  - North Carolina, 1944; 1 (Box 34)
  - Columbia, 1945; 2 (Box 35, Box 44)
  - Cornell, 1945; 1 (Box 36)
  - Dartmouth, 1945; 1 (Box 37)
  - Coast Guard, 1945; 1 (Box 38)
  - Tufts, 1945; 1 (Box 39)
  - Holy Cross, 1945; 1 (Box 40)
  - Princeton, 1945; 1 (Box 41)
  - Princeton Highlights, 1945; 1 (Box 42)
  - Summer Scrimmage, 1945; 1 (Box 43)
  - Cornell, 1945; 3 (Box 45–47)
  - Harvard Highlights, 1945; 2 (Box 48–49)
  - Inter squad, 1945; 1 (Box 50)
  - Colgate, 1946; 3 (Box 52–54)
  - Coast Guard, 1946; 3 (Box 55–57)
    - Use copy for boxes 55-57, 1 (Box 55U)
  - Princeton, 1946; 4 (Box 58–61)
    - Use copy for boxes 58-61, 1 (Box 58U)
  - Harvard and Princeton, 1946; 1 (Box 62)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 62U)
  - Harvard, 1946; 2 (Box 63, Box 69)
    - Use copy for boxes 63 and 69, 1 (Box 63U)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1946; 1 (Box 64)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1946; 2 (Box 65–66)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1946; 1 (Box 67)
  - Spring Practice, 1946; 1 (Box 68)
  - Kings Point, 1947; 3 (Box 70–72)
  - Cornell, 1947; 3 (Box 73–75)
  - Wisconsin, 1947; 4 (Box 76–79)
  - Springfield, 1947; 3 (Box 80–82)
  - Dartmouth, 1947; 3 (Box 83–85)
  - Brown, 1947; 3 (Box 86–88)
  - Princeton, 1947; 3 (Box 89–91)
  - Harvard, 1947; 4 (Box 92–95)
    - Use copy for boxes 92-95, 1 (Box 92U)
  - Harvard Highlights, 1947; 2 (Box 96–97)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1947; 1 (Box 98)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1947; 1 (Box 99)
  - Scrimmage vs. Holy Cross, 1947; 1 (Box 100)
  - Scrimmage vs. Army, 1947; 1 (Box 101)
  - Spring Practice, 1947; 2 (Box 102–103)
- Football game films, 1948-1950; Accession 2006-A-134
  - UConn, 1948; 3 (Box 1–3)
  - Columbia, 1948; 3 (Box 4–6)
  - Wisconsin, 1948; 3 (Box 7–9)
    - Use copy for boxes 7-9, 1 (Box 7U)
  - Vanderbilt, 1948; 4 (Box 10–12, Box 109)
  - Dartmouth, 1948; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Kings Point, 1948; 4 (Box 17–20)
  - Princeton, 1948; 4 (Box 21–24)
  - Harvard, 1948; 3 (Box 25–27)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1948; 2 (Box 28–29)
  - Freshmen vs. Holy Cross, 1948; 2 (Box 30–31)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1948; 2 (Box 32–33)
  - Scrimmages
    - 1st Spring, 1948; 1 (Box 34)
    - 3rd Spring, 1948; 2 (Box 35–36)
    - 4th Spring, 1948; film reel (16mm) (Box 37)
    - Last Spring, 1948; 2 (Box 38–39)
    - Final Spring, 1948; 1 (Box 40)
    - Spring, 1948; 1 (Box 41)
  - "Touchdown" Navy, 1948; 1 (Box 42)
  - UConn, 1949; 3 (Box 43–45)
  - Columbia, 1949; 4 (Box 46–49)
    - Use copy for boxes 46-49, 1 (Box 46U)
  - Cornell, 1949; 4 (Box 50–53)
    - Use copy for boxes 50-53, 1 (Box 50U)
  - Holy Cross, 1949; 3 (Box 54–56)
  - Dartmouth, 1949; 3 (Box 57–59)
  - Brown, 1949; 3 (Box 60–62)
    - Use copy for boxes 60-62, 1 (Box 60U)
  - Princeton, 1949; 3 (Box 63–65)
    - Use copy for boxes 63-65, 1 (Box 63U)
  - Harvard, 1949; 3 (Box 66–68)
    - Use copy for boxes 66-68, 1 (Box 66U)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1949; 2 (Box 69–70)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1949; 1 (Box 71)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1949; 2 (Box 72–73)
  - Freshmen vs. Andover, 1949; 3 (Box 74–76)
  - UConn, 1950; 3 (Box 77, Box 112–113)
  - Brown, 1950; 3 (Box 78–80)
    - Use copy for boxes 78-80, 1 (Box 78U)
  - Fordham, 1950; 3 (Box 81–83)
  - Columbia, 1950; 3 (Box 84–85, Box 110)
  - Columbia/Fordham highlights, 1950; 1 (Box 86)
  - Cornell, 1950; 3 (Box 87–89)
  - Holy Cross, 1950; 2 (Box 90–91)
    - Use copy for boxes 90-91, 1 (Box 90U)
  - Dartmouth, 1950; 3 (Box 92–93, Box 111)
  - Princeton, 1950; 3 (Box 94–96)
  - Harvard, 1950; 3 (Box 97–99)
    - Use copy for boxes 97-99, 1; videotape (VHS) (Box 97U)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1950; 3 (Box 100–102)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1950; 2 (Box 103–104)
  - Scrimmage vs. Springfield, 1950; 1 (Box 105)
  - Scrimmage vs. R.H.I.S., 1950; 2 (Box 106–107)
  - North/ South All Stars, 1950; 1 (Box 108)
- Football game films, 1951-1953; Accession 2006-A-135
  - Bates, 1951; 3 (Box 1–3)
  - Navy, 1951; 4 (Box 4–7)
  - Brown, 1951; 3 (Box 8–10)
  - Columbia, 1951; 3 (Box 11–13)
  - Cornell, 1951; 3 (Box 14–16)
  - Colgate, 1951; 4 (Box 17–20)
  - Dartmouth, 1951; 3 (Box 21–23)
  - Princeton, 1951; 3 (Box 24–26)
  - Harvard, 1951; 3 (Box 27–29)
  - Season Highlights, 1951; 1 (Box 30)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1951; 3 (Box 31–33)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1951; 3 (Box 34–36)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1951; 2 (Box 37–38)
  - UConn, 1952; 2 (Box 39–40)
  - Navy, 1952; 3 (Box 41–43)
  - Brown, 1952; 3 (Box 44–46)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 44U)
  - Columbia, 1952; 3 (Box 47–49)
  - Cornell, 1952; 3 (Box 50–52)
  - Lafayette, 1952; 3 (Box 53–55)
  - Princeton, 1952; 3 (Box 56–58)
  - Harvard, 1952; 3 (Box 59–61)
  - Season Highlights, 1952; 2 (Box 62–63)
    - Use copy for boxes 62-63, 1 (Box 62U)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1952; 3 (Box 64–66)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1952; 1 (Box 67)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1952; 1 (Box 68)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1952; 1 (Box 69)
  - UConn, 1953; 3 (Box 70–72)
  - Brown, 1953; 3 (Box 73–75)
  - Columbia, 1953; 3 (Box 76–78)
  - Cornell, 1953; 3 (Box 79–81)
  - Colgate, 1953; 3 (Box 82–84)
  - Dartmouth, 1953; 3 (Box 85–87)
  - Temple, 1953; 3 (Box 88–90)
  - Princeton, 1953; 4 (Box 91–94)
    - Use copy for reels 1 and 3, 1 (Box 91A)
  - Harvard, 1953; 3 (Box 95–97)
  - Season Highlights, 1953; 1 (Box 98)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 98U)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1953; 3 (Box 99–101)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1953; 1 (Box 102)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1953; 2 (Box 103–104)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1953; 1 (Box 105)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1953; 1 (Box 106)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1953; 1 (Box 107)
  - Scrimmage vs. Boston College, 1953; 3 (Box 108–110)
- Football game films, 1954-1956; Accession 2006-A-154
  - UConn, 1954; 3 (Box 1–3)
  - Brown, 1954; 3 (Box 4–6)
  - Columbia, 1954; 2 (Box 7–8)
  - Cornell, 1954; 3 (Box 9–11)
  - Colgate, 1954; 3 (Box 12–14)
  - Dartmouth, 1954; 3 (Box 15–17)
  - Army, 1954; 3 (Box 18–20)
  - Princeton, 1954; 3 (Box 21–23)
  - Harvard, 1954; 3 (Box 24–26)
  - Season Highlights, 1954; 1 (Box 27)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 27U1)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 27U2)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1954; 2 (Box 28–29)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1954; 1 (Box 30)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1954; 1 (Box 31)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1954; 1 (Box 32)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1954; 1 (Box 33)
  - UConn, 1955; 3 (Box 34–36)
  - Brown, 1955; 3 (Box 37–39)
  - Columbia, 1955; 3 (Box 40–42)
  - Cornell, 1955; 3 (Box 43–45)
  - Colgate, 1955; 4 (Box 46–49)
  - Dartmouth, 1955; 4 (Box 50–53)
  - Army, 1955; 4 (Box 54–57)
  - Princeton, 1955; 4 (Box 58–61)
  - Harvard, 1955; 3 (Box 62–64)
  - Season's Highlights, 1955; 1 (Box 65)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 65U)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1955; 1 (Box 66)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1955; 1 (Box 67)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1955; 1 (Box 68)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1955; 1 (Box 69)
  - Freshmen highlights, 1955; 1 (Box 70)
  - UConn, 1956; 3 (Box 71–73)
  - Brown, 1956; 4 (Box 74–77)
  - Columbia, 1956; 4 (Box 78–81)
  - Cornell, 1956; 4 (Box 82–85)
  - Colgate, 1956; 4 (Box 86–89)
    - Use copy for boxes 86-89, 1 (Box 86U)
  - Dartmouth, 1956; 3 (Box 90–92)
  - Penn, 1956; 4 (Box 93–96)
  - Princeton [reel 5 in color with narration], 1956; 5 (Box 97–101)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 97U)
  - Harvard, 1956; 4 (Box 102–105)
    - Use copy for boxes 102-105, 1 (Box 102U)
  - Sports TV Presents All-American Game of the Week with Tom Harman [Yale vs. Princeton?], 1956; 1 (Box 106)
  - Harvard, 1956; 1 (Box 107)
  - Season Highlights, 1956; 1 (Box 108)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 108U)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1956; 3 (Box 109–111)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1956; 1 (Box 112)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1956; 1 (Box 113)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1956; 1 (Box 114)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1956; 1 (Box 115)
- Football game films, 1957-1959; Accession 2006-A-155
  - UConn, 1957; 4 (Box 1–4)
  - Brown, 1957; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - Columbia, 1957; 4 (Box 9–12)
  - Cornell, 1957; 4 (Box 13–16)
  - Colgate, 1957; 4 (Box 17–20)
  - Dartmouth, 1957; 4 (Box 21–24)
  - Penn, 1957; 4 (Box 25–28)
  - Princeton, 1957; 4 (Box 29–32)
  - Princeton highlights, 1957; 1 (Box 133)
  - Harvard, 1957; 4 (Box 33–36)
  - Harvard highlights, 1957; 1 (Box 37)
  - Yale Ivy League highlights, 1957; 1 (Box 38)
    Filmed by George Weber; music by Yale Band; narrated by Jordan Olivar, football coach.
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 38U)
  - Princeton-deep coverage, 1957; 1 (Box 39)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1957; 2 (Box 128–129)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1957; 1 (Box 130)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1957; 1 (Box 131)
  - UConn, 1958; 4 (Box 40–43)
  - Brown, 1958; 4 (Box 44–47)
  - Columbia, 1958; 4 (Box 48–51)
  - Cornell, 1958; 4 (Box 52–55)
  - Colgate, 1958; 4 (Box 56–59)
  - Dartmouth, 1958; 4 (Box 60–63)
  - Penn, 1958; 4 (Box 64–67)
  - Princeton, 1958; 4 (Box 68–71)
  - Harvard, 1958; 4 (Box 72–75)
  - Season highlights, 1958; 1 (Box 76)
    Narrated by Jordan Olivar, football coach.
  - Season highlights, 1958; 1 (Box 132)
    Filmed by George Weber; music by Yale Band.
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1958; 2 (Box 77–78)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1958; 2 (Box 79–80)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1958; 4 (Box 81–82)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1958; 1 (Box 83)
  - Yale vs. Penn and Harvard, 1958; 1 (Box 84)
  - UConn, 1959; 4 (Box 85–88)
  - Brown, 1959; 4 (Box 89–92)
  - Columbia, 1959; 4 (Box 93–96)
  - Cornell, 1959; 4 (Box 97–100)
  - Colgate, 1959; 4 (Box 101–104)
  - Dartmouth, 1959; 4 (Box 105–108)
  - Penn, 1959; 4 (Box 109–112)
  - Princeton, 1959; 4 (Box 113–116)
  - Harvard, 1959; 4 (Box 117–120)
  - Season highlights, 1959; 1 (Box 121)
    Title: Alumni Board presents Yale Football Ivy League Highlights 1959; narrated by head coach Jordan Olivar.
  - Freshman vs. Princeton, 1959; 3 (Box 122–124)
  - Freshman vs. Cornell, 1959; 1 (Box 125)
  - JV vs. Dartmouth, 1959; 2 (Box 126–127)
- Football game films, 1960-1962; Accession 2006-A-156
  - UConn, 1960; 4 (Box 1–4)
  - Brown, 1960; 4 (Box 5–8)
  - Columbia, 1960; 4 (Box 9–12)
  - Cornell, 1960; 3 (Box 13–15)
  - Colgate, 1960; 4 (Box 16–19)
  - Dartmouth, 1960; 4 (Box 20–23)
  - Penn, 1960; 4 (Box 24–27)
    - Use copy for boxes 24-27, 1 (Box 24U)
  - Princeton (2nd half), 1960; 2 (Box 28–29)
  - Telenews highlights of Harvard (game filmed by James M. Banner '30), 1960 November 19; 1 (Box 30)
    - Duplicating Master, 6
    - Use Copy, 1 (Box 30U)
  - Season highlights, 1960; 1 (Box 31)
    Title: Ivy League Championship Football Highlights 1960; narrated by Jordan Olivar; filmed by George Weber; music by Yale Band and Glee Club.
    - Duplicating Master, 7
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 31U1)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 31U2)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 1960; 2 (Box 32–33)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1960; 2 (Box 34–35)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1960?; 2 (Box 36–37)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1960; 1 (Box 79)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1960; 1 (Box 145)
  - UConn, 1961; 4 (Box 38–41)
  - Brown, 1961; 4 (Box 42–45)
  - Columbia, 1961; 4 (Box 46–49)
  - Cornell, 1961; 4 (Box 50–53)
  - Colgate, 1961; 4 (Box 54–57)
  - Dartmouth, 1961; 4 (Box 58–61)
    - Use copy for boxes 58-61, 1 (Box 58U)
  - Penn, 1961; 4 (Box 62–65)
    - Use copy for boxes 62-65, 1 (Box 62U)
  - Princeton, 1961; 4 (Box 66–69)
  - Harvard, 1961; 4 (Box 70–73)
  - Season highlights, 1961; 1 (Box 74)
    Narrated by Jordan Olivar; music by Yale Band and Glee Club; filmed by George Weber.
  - JV vs. Navy, 1961; 4 (Box 75–78)
  - Freshmen vs. Dartmouth, 1961; 2 (Box 80–81)
  - Freshmen vs. Brown, 2 (Box 82–83)
  - Freshmen vs. Harvard, 1961; 3 (Box 84–86)
  - Freshmen vs. Princeton, 1961; 3 (Box 87–89)
  - Freshmen vs. Columbia, 1961; 2 (Box 90–91)
  - Freshmen vs. Cornell, 1961; 1 (Box 92)
  - UConn, 1962; 4 (Box 93–96)
  - Brown, 1962; 4 (Box 97–100)
  - Columbia, 1962; 4 (Box 101–104)
  - Cornell, 1962; 4 (Box 105–108)
  - Colgate, 1962; 4 (Box 109–112)
  - Dartmouth, 1962; 4 (Box 113–116)
  - Penn, 1962; 4 (Box 117–120)
    - Use copy, 1 (Box 117U)
  - Princeton, 1962; 6 (Box 121–126)